All right. Really, really pleased with
the way our guys responded this week,
played um just building off off of what
we thought was a good game last week,
particularly in the second half. Just
challenge those guys to to show up and
and keep that momentum going. And so
they did. Absolutely did. And um I
thought defensively, you know, really
shutting down the run game, not giving
them anything in the run game early on.
Um outside of that one touchdown early
in the game, I thought that they played
really good. you know, got a lot of
pressure on on Jacobe, four sacks, bunch
of TFLs, really harassed him throughout
the night. Uh, that was awesome to see.
Three of 13 on third down was critical
for us. And then offensively, uh, you
know, just scoring points on six of
those first seven drives there to really
establish, you know, control of the game
and and be able to finish it the right
way. So, so really pleased. I thought
the kicking game was good, too. Great
punt return. Um, good job with the punts
down at the end of the game. Evan had a
big one. I think 57 yards, you know, at
a key point there to to extend the lead
to nine there in the second quarter.
That was a key key kick for us. Um, so
just overall pleased with the way that
everybody approached the game.
>> How long was Tony Ford play?
>> Uh, one week. You know, we had with with
Noah going into the week not knowing how
we were going to have Noah, we had a lot
of heavier 12 personnel groupings where
he was going to be out there. And so
just to keep the guys, you know, in the
O line room, keep that energy sky high.
Not that I I need to create anything to
do that, but um, we practiced it. He
caught it during the week and then felt
like the right moment to get it called.
Were you aware it was his birthday today
factor into
>> I'm not aware of people's birthdays in
general. Okay. Just to be crystal clear.
So always assume that I I don't know
that information till after the game.
>> What did you make of the crowd reaction?
I think they were unhappy that he was
taken off the field. Did you catch wind
of that in real time or
>> No, I No, you're you're in play calling
mode at that point. So you you don't
have great awareness on what's
happening.
>> Was there a thought of giving it to him
again?
>> No. No chance. Z% chance. 0% chance.
>> Is that the throw? Is that where it's
designed to go? Like read?
>> I mean, yes. the the yes that was the
one play where we would like to get him
the ball. The corner played pretty tight
to start and then I think Joe kind of
gave some shoulders to loosen him up and
then came back to him. So he usually
goes out there a little quicker but they
were they were taking it away so Joe
softened him up a little bit. Um made a
good throwing catch.
>> Was there any yards after a catch in the
practice rout?
>> No, it was uh well there's no contact
really in practice. I was I was right
there. I mean he I was there. I wanted
him just to go down, get the four, go
down, put us in the second, six, and he
just kept kept breaking tackles. That
was pretty impressive.
>> In Cody Ford, Jamar Chase breaks his
drought.
How nice was it to see him get off the
Schneider early in this game?
>> Yeah. Uh, I mean I I really wasn't aware
of it until T pointed out in the last
game, you know, during the game and and
so we're just going to go out there and
call it the way we see it. You know,
that this play he scored on is just, you
know, a play we've run 100 times and um
he did a great job, you know, making
people miss and getting in the end zone.
And then the other one before the half
was just, you know, um really good play
design there by Ruscotti and pitch and
and uh so that one worked out well.
Zack, what does this do for Joe Burrow
coming back from injury this season
playing in these games even though
you're out of the playoffs to to have
this kind of good play to see it look
like this when he's healthy?
>> Yeah, I mean we we've seen this from
Joe. Um he's got a ton of confidence.
He's playing with great rhythm,
>> extending plays, hitting big plays down
the field. Uh did a great job with the
protection checks today because that can
be really difficult and stressful
against these guys. They do a good job
of attacking your protections and so Joe
was on it. Um, and so again, just he
he's he's playing like I know Joe to
play and it's fun to watch.
>> Chase Brown, another huge game. What has
made him so consistent over the last
eight weeks?
>> Yeah. Well, he's very versatile with how
you can utilize him. Um, at the same
time, I think our lineman is doing a
great They're doing a great job in the
run game, too. So giving him sorry
giving him great opportunity in the run
game um to get those get those yards
beyond the line of scrimmage and he's
doing a great job making people missing
space and uh playing through contact at
the second level and and had you know I
don't know how many explosives today but
they were they were significant runs
that put us in a really good position.
>> Chase had Chase Brown had five
touchdowns in the third quarter over the
last two weeks. The third quarter three
last week two of this any rhyme or
reason to that?
>> No. No. I mean, it's it's certainly when
we're at halftime, um, we got to come
out with a mentality and the defense has
really set the tone the last two weeks
and the offense has countered off of
that. So, I was really pleased to see us
get, you know, the the the two quick
stops from the defense and then counter
two touchdowns from the offense. Um,
then you get a chance, you know, as the
fourth quarter hits to to get some other
guys in there and keep playing football.
But, uh, just I was really proud of the
way that the guys came out and attacked
post halftime and established the game
for us and let us gain control. He's
pretty loud in that.
>> Miles Murphy making the plays that he's
making when
>> Yeah, he's just he's ascended all
season. Um he's put in great work. He
has a lot of confidence right now. I
think Jerry's doing a great job with
him. He's taking all those things to
heart and really just stepping up his
game and that's that's been fun to
watch.
>> Is that an example of how important
these final games for a guy like
>> Sure. I mean, he he's, you know, going
to have finish it up the right way next
week and and have a lot of confidence
going to the offseason and seeing what
it can look like. And I think our
defense as a whole, that's just what's
been really fun for me to see and it
should be for everybody. Just their
confidence continues to increase and and
they understand um exactly what we're
asking them to do and and they're
starting to do it at a high level and
and so just really proud of those guys
sticking together, you know, through
through everything that's happened this
season. Coaches, players, just just keep
pushing forward and persevering and um
they're having a lot of fun right now.
>> Pretty loud in that locker room after
the game, especially with those Cody
chants that we could hear. What was the
message in there? And what was like
seeing him get
>> We have to finish this off the right
way, you know, and it's all we can
control right now is what we got in
front of us. It's one game left. Three
practices. Um got to go finish this
thing the right way like these guys have
been doing for us and um you know, just
again important to to play well in front
of our home fans, you know, and and
finish this out the right way.
>> Was out at one point, kind of came back
in. How did that go in terms of did he
say I want to get back in though or how
did that end up?
>> Yeah, he had a great mindset. You know,
he had a a Shane that we needed to let
rest for at least a series and then he
was able to go back out there. So, I was
proud of him and then at the end of the
game, you know, we wanted to get some
other guys in.
>> Ride had some catches later on in the
game, but for the most part, you guys
did a really good job containing him.
Obviously, you know, receptions leader
in the league. What was the focus this
week heading into this one?
>> Well, I I thought Al had a great plan.
All and his staff had a great plan to
try to minimize all of that and not make
anything easy for them offensively. And
so I I know his production, his catches,
he got a bunch there at the end and he's
a he's a heck of a player um that I'm
really impressed with and and I thought
our defense did a really good job keying
in and making things really difficult
for Arizona.
>> Zack, I think Shamar got to Jacobe,
brought him down today. Do you kind of
like Miles, do you feel like that's a
player who's wrapping this up in
>> I mean, he he hasn't got a chance to
just be healthy for a long stretch. It's
always a stop start this year, no no
fault of his own with these injuries and
so to see him out there and again just
he's accumulating a bunch of snaps over
these last couple weeks and to get his
first career sack and kind of get that
get that off your back a little bit
before you're going into the offseason
and um so again, he's got he's got a lot
of potential for us.
>> Do you plan to have Joe play again next
week?
>> Yes. What do you think it meant for
Shamar to get that first sack
considering, you know, like you said, up
and down, he's been out multiple times
with injuries. What do you think it
meant to him?
>> I think it's meaningful, you know, for
for a guy who's who's been working
through it, injuries, rookie year, all
the challenges that comes with it. Um,
again, just to check that box, that's
done. Now, let's go get a lot more.
>> How gratifying is it for you personally
to put together some uh highscoring
performances at the end of this season?
It's the gratifying part for me is that
this team has uh maintained their energy
through some really difficult times and
really stuck together when people
question what what they're going to see
from us. Um there should be no question
that you know this team is is made of
the right stuff and and I think that's
just the part that I focus on that we
have a great group of coaches that have
really stuck together and kept coaching.
Um, and these players have bought into
it and provided tremendous energy for us
and and the proof has been playing these
last two weeks on the field and and
that's all we can control right now is
every game that's in front of us and how
we're going to react to it and um so
again, we got to do that for one more
week.
>> Okay. Thank you.